weareteachers.com 2011-12-31

# We Are Teachers | Privacy Policy

## **WEARETEACHERS.COM, LLC  
PRIVACY POLICY**

WeAreTeachers has established this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect personal information about you, and how this information is used by us. Any capitalized terms used and not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in the WeAreTeachers [Terms of Use](http://www.weareteachers.com/terms-of-use).

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. We will do our best to keep you abreast of these changes by posting a notice regarding the new Privacy Policy as well as the new Privacy Policy itself on the Site. You should visit this page periodically to review the Privacy Policy because it is binding on you.

We take protecting your personal information very seriously. That being said, we would ask you to be careful and use caution when providing personal information, including in User Content which you post to or otherwise transmit using the Site or when you communicate with Teachers, Learners, and other users. Unfortunately, there is no way we can be responsible for their actions.

By using, accessing or registering on the Site, you agree (a) to comply with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and (b) that WeAreTeachers and any Teacher, Learner, or other user may process (i.e., use, collect, etc.) your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service. Personal information may be processed by WeAreTeachers or the Teacher, Learner, or other user in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of personal information may be less stringent.

### **Children under Age 13**

WeAreTeachers does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for WeAreTeachers or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on WeAreTeachers or use the Site in any way. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@weareteachers.com](mailto:support@weareteachers.com).

### Children between the Ages of 13 and 18

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### **Collection and Use of Information from Subscribers**

### Browsing the Site

You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you register as a member of WeAreTeachers, you are not anonymous to WeAreTeachers.

### Becoming a Member

To become a member of WeAreTeachers, you must first complete the registration forms found on the Site. To establish a User ID and password, we require your name and e-mail address. This information is stored on WeAreTeachers' secure servers and is not shared with any outside parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. If you forget your password, follow the process set up by WeAreTeachers and a new password will be sent to you.

We may also use your registration information

  * •to verify access rights to the Service;
  * •in connection with transactions facilitated through the Site, including to purchase and sell User Content and services;
  * •to provide you with personalized content programming, instructions and services;
  * •to provide you with information, through the Site or via e-mail, about our (and our affiliates) products and services as well as news, events, and promotions;
  * •to send you administrative messages and email updates regarding your membership (including fees owed or earned);
  * •for assessment of service levels;
  * •to better understand on an aggregated basis how our (and our affiliates) products are used, gauge traffic patterns and determine what types of content and services are most popular with users of our products and services.

You may opt out of receiving administrative messages, email updates, and other notices by canceling your WeAreTeachers membership.

We also collect credit card and billing information to complete the registration. WeAreTeachers stores this information for the length of the billing period since subscription fees are recurring on an annual basis until your subscription is terminated. Such credit card information is removed and destroyed once a subscription has been terminated.

To protect your WeAreTeachers login ID, please keep your password secure.

### Posting User Content on the Site

Once you are a member of WeAreTeachers, you are able to post User Content on the Site, including to create a profile containing basic information about yourself (your name, e-mail address, and other contact information) as well as more detailed profile containing professional and personal data about you. This may include past jobs, areas of expertise, and individual "claims to fame". You can post photos, too!

Once submitted, User Content will be made available to other users of the Site. You may access, correct, update, and delete the information in your User Content at any time by logging into the Site using your login ID and password, and choosing Edit My Profile. User Content will remain available to other users until you request that it be removed from our active database. To do so, contact WeAreTeachers via email at [support@weareteachers.com](mailto:support@weareteachers.com) or cancel your WeAreTeachers membership in which case the Content will be made unavailable through the Service. WeAreTeachers will try to execute changes to the User Content available on the Site promptly typically within two business days.

### Sharing User Content

Your first and last names are displayed throughout the Site and are therefore available to the public. Other people can see User Content you make available, the services you offer, your online journal, feedback that is posted, ratings and associated comments, and so on in addition to your profile. Therefore, if you include your registration information or any other personal information in User Content that you post to the Site or sell using the Service, that information may be widely available to other users since WeAreTeachers does not delete or redact registration or other information from Content you provide. WeAreTeachers does not control that disclosure, and is not liable in any way for anyone's use or misuse of the information in the disclosure. So be careful about the information you choose to disclose if you do not want your personal information to be displayed as part of your User Content, don't include it in the Content! In other words, use caution and judgment here.

And remember: you may not include personal information about other people in User Content. You also may not use personal information about other users of WeAreTeachers in a way that is inconsistent with WeAreTeachers' Privacy Policy. If you do, you will have violated the terms of this Agreement, and WeAreTeachers may terminate your membership. WeAreTeachers is not liable for any damage that may be incurred due to use of registration or other personal information that was made available as part of User Content.

### Receiving Payments for Recommendations

In order to receive payments from recommendations that result in a transaction, as more fully described in our Supplemental Terms and Conditions, you will have to provide additional information when you register. This may include the name, address, and phone number where you would like to receive your payment. Since payment will be made via PayPal, we will ask for your PayPal username in order to process your payment.

Your earnings from making recommendations are subject to US tax laws. Therefore, in order to receive payment, you will have to complete the Taxpayer Information section. We ask for your SSN, TIN, or EIN for the sole purpose of issuing a 1099 form for your earnings.

### Receiving Payments from Learners

The purchase of User Content, a service or other products from a Teacher or a third party vendor is strictly between the Learner who is purchasing the Content, product or service and the Teacher or other vendor selling it. WeAreTeachers is not involved in the actual transaction between Learner and Teacher (or other vendor). For payment processing purposes, only PayPal is accepted. Therefore, any disclosure of your PayPal username is strictly to facilitate the purchase of User Content, services, and other products. Visit <https://www.paypal.com/> to learn more about PayPal.

### Cookies and Passive Data Collection

In order to improve the Service and the Site, we use cookies when you are logged into the Site using your login ID and password. A cookie is a piece of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be understood by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your computer's identification token and enables WeAreTeachers to personalize your experience when you are using the Site or Service. If you reject the cookie, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)

While WeAreTeachers uses cookies to enable you to use the Services and the Site, like most Internet services, we use log files, both on the client and server side. The data held in log files includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, browser type, e-mail application, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit Web pages, computer platform type, date/time stamp, and user activity. WeAreTeachers uses server log data to analyze trends, administer the Service and the Site, and improve service levels. IP addresses may be disclosed to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process requires it, or to protect the rights or property of WeAreTeachers, our users or the general public.

### Third Party Websites

Users should be aware that other websites visited before entering WeAreTeachers might place personally identifiable information within a User's URL during a visit to their website, and WeAreTeachers has no control over such websites. Accordingly, some of this information may be logged by a subsequent website that collects URL information.

### **Disclosures of Information to Third Parties**

WeAreTeachers may need to provide your registration and other personal information to third parties as described in this section.

### . . . to Service Providers

WeAreTeachers may need to provide your registration and other personal information to third parties to deliver specific services to you (such as hosting services, support services, or credit card payment processing).

### . . . to Law Enforcement

WeAreTeachers may disclose registration and any other personal information if required by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order, where required by law, or, at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to protect the safety of any individual or the general public or to prevent violation of our Terms of Service or the rights of WeAreTeachers or any third party.

### . . . to Affiliates

Although WeAreTeachers currently does not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, affiliates), it may in the future. WeAreTeachers may share some of all of your personal information with these affiliates, in which case we will seek to require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

### . . . in the Event of a Change in Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of WeAreTeachers's registration information and User Content, including email addresses, to a separate entity. WeAreTeachers will notify users via a posting on this site or email (in WeAreTeachers's discretion) of such a transfer, and users may choose to modify their registration information at that time. This means if you are concerned about your personal information migrating to a new owner, you can deactivate your account.

### Security

WeAreTeachers uses industry standard security measures (Secure Socket Layer (SSL)) to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by WeAreTeachers in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, WeAreTeachers cannot guarantee complete security. Further, while we work hard to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

### Updating or Removing User Information

Users may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information they have submitted to WeAreTeachers, by going to their account. Even if you update or remove your information, however, it may be retained in our backup files and archives.

Members may remove their user information from WeAreTeachers by canceling their membership.

### Changes to the WeAreTeachers Privacy Policy

If we change the Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on the Site with a link from the Site's homepage, so that you are always able to determine what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any we disclose it.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the Privacy Policy, please contact WeAreTeachers.com, L.L.C. at our Austin headquarters located at 8015 Shoal Creek Blvd., Suite 100, Austin, TX 78757.
